I said it before, and I will say it again.
It is not enough to simply just be black.
You have to be black, and you have to be about breaking down the imperialist empire that continues to use your blackness against you.
You have to be committed to breaking down the imperialist empire that is allowing other countries to be used against you.
And anyone who is supporting that is not getting my support.
Black or not.
At the end of the day, we must honor those who are brave enough to put their futures on the line for causes that end up supporting everybody's elevation.
An example of that is these students that are currently protesting.
The same students who, though peacefully protesting, are having the same militarized state-sanctioned police force put upon them that we as black people in this country have been fighting against since we were let out of slavery and into their hands.
So miss me with any kumbaya bullshit that is expected, because at the end of the day, we can no longer support black people who are supporting any structures that are propping up the white supremacy that continues to oppress us.
Period.
Someone asked me today, don't you ever get tired of standing on business?
No.
I was born on business.
Pa-dum-bum!